Cory Dominguez

Coordinates

Software developer residing in Mountain View CA. Check out my github.com/corydominguez or linkedin.com/in/corydominguez for more detail.

If you would like to contact me please try the following methods (ordered by efficiency):

- corydominguez@gmail.com
- (347) 725-0527
- enigma machine

Summary of Qualifications

- 2 years industry experience.
- Experience designing, implementing and scaling mySQL databases.
- Excellent scripting skills and general commandline-fu.
- Collaborated on large projects using Version Control.
- Side projects in Android and Play/Scala.

Technical Profile

(ordered by competency)

Programing Languages: Python, Java, Groovy, Bash, Scala, HTML, CSS

Frameworks / Libraries: Grails, Android, Play, Google App Engine, Flask, Less, Twitter Bootstrap, Yeoman

API's / Protocols: REST, SOAP, XML-RPC, Twitter, Magento, Shopify, Bigcommerce

Databases: MySQL, SQLite, SequelPro

Tools: Git, SSH, Regular Expressions, OpenSSL, Sublime Text, IntelliJ IDEA, vim

Work History

Yahoo

Channel Commando - Software Engineer Level IC 2 August 2013 - present

Transferred with acquisition of Lexity by Yahoo, integrated Yahoo Store, as a result participated in scaling the system to support the 10x increase in users.

Lexity

Channel Commando January 2013 - August 2013

- Owner and maintainer of the Channelmanager component, a groovy on grails project with mySQL which extracts product and order information from several ecommerce platforms including Shopify, Bigcommerce, Magento, Volusion, Etsy, eBay, Prestashop...
- Refactored and improved quality and speed of every major platform
- Increased the amount of platforms supported by 30%.

Pacific Wave Board Shop

Chief Button Sorter August 2011 - December 2012

- http://pacwave.com is a ecommerce website using the Magento platform.
- Helped redesign in early 2012.
- Scripted the automation of product creation and inventory update using a custom magento api library resulting in a 30x increase in efficiency. A piece of it can be seen at http://github.com/corydominguez/pacwave-importer

Projects

Android

Completed Codepath Android development class at Yahoo. You can see my progression in the following repositories:

- http://github.com/corydominguez/tiptastic
- http://github.com/corydominguez/tifftastic
- http://github.com/corydominguez/tweetastic
- http://github.com/corydominguez/sqrl-android
- http://github.com/corydominguez/sqrl-server

Coursera Functional Programing in Scala

(incomplete) I have documented the work I did in this repository: http://github.com/corydominguez/fp-scala

Cal Query

My first web application, it generates HTML invoices from google calendar data using python, webapp2 and google app engine. http://github.com/corydominguez/calquery

Education